Hi, in this lesson, I will help you to quickly start this course of AI,
record the data, and I will show you briefly some popular features
how to use the Google Heaven overview, what is course or, and what you can do with it.
And of course, in the next lesson, I will go deeper into every feature.
I will explain how you can use it all the options,
so we really recommend you to watch all the lessons.
Okay, now we need to create a new project.
I will create the folder, which is names equal saw, dash AI,
and then we will use it as project folder.
Here we can click open project,
and I will open my projects to saw dash AI.
Okay, from the left side, you will see all the files and folder we will have
at the sidebar, in a center, you will have the code open at files,
and at the right side, you will have the chart panel.
Okay, now let's create a new file.
I will name it currency converter, and we will test with you how course or
view do the suggestions for this project.
Dot chess.
When you provide a file name, or saw review use, this file name as the context,
so you will understand the spiral about currency converter,
and he can provide more accurate logic.
I want to show you how work will stop completion.
We of course will have a separate lesson about it,
where I will go in details, but let's see and over you how this feature works.
So when we start typing something, or saw will try to predict what we want to
write, and do the suggestions.
All let's write plus, I want to implement currency converter class.
So to do the suggestion, we can accept it by clicking on top, and now we see the logic.
It's a jesus to implement.
I can click on a set.
I don't like this logic, because it's not really reusable.
We need to every time creating new class instance, where we provide
amount from currency to currency, so it's not really reusable.
And I want to have some generic currency converter method class,
where I can provide, for example, some rates, yeah, to convert doors to euro,
on another side.
And then I want to use some method to where you can provide an amount and
currencies from a tool, yeah, and do the conversion, and do it for multiple
amounts, like make it reusable.
Now I gonna select the constructor.
You see it suggests it's convert method, but it's not reusable.
I selected the constructor code, and I will show you how work with online
suggestion, sorry, with online chat.
You can click on command plus key, or if you use windows, use control plus key.
I mean, okay, and you can provide some prompt right here, and I will ask him to
make this class more generic, as that I can use it or
mouse to pull the amount on the versions.
Let's see how it can implement it.
Do it really bad, so it just, I want to show you an example, so what you
will provide is that it will return to euro.
So if you wanted to get more accurate results, you need to provide some
like detailed instructions to what you expect from AI, because it's
don't read your source.
So let's now provide a really good prompt what you want to achieve, so I
want to have a convert constructor, with rates, and the method convert,
I can provide, I can provide an amount and roll and do our answers.
Okay, we have a constructor with rates, we have convert method, we will check
across the case, if there is rates for these currencies, if no, you say message, it's not
available, okay, it's good.
Yes, and we define a rate from into rate, then we define the base amount and convert
the amount, okay, it's fine, and then if you return us some default amount from
currency to currency and convert it amount, okay, it looks good for us, much
better, like we got that, okay, and let's see how work we use a chart interface
from the right side, I can ask any questions or write some prompts right here,
I'll imagine we want to have some default rates to not provide it every time, so
and I will ask it to set some default rates, for example, for five, the most popular
currencies, set default rates for five, most popular currencies, okay, let's wait, it's
need a bit of time to generate it, get rid of our currency convert to digest file, and you see
right here, it generated some default rates, and for example, he defines the rates, it
mirrors the default rates and some rates we can provide, so if you not provide the rates,
it will use default rates, otherwise, it will be used, so we can override some default
rates, let's see, as a convert, method looks same, and below he just show us example, yeah,
this is what I want to achieve, like we use the currency convert, convert method with
different amounts and different conversions, so just click accept, so we can click accept
right here at your accept all the changes, okay, I like it more, you see it even added
a comment that this Chinese yuan, Japanese yen, British pound, euro, US stores, uses the
base currency, so he also provides some comments, okay, we can also use in line chart making
some fixes, let's imagine we have palm logic broken, I don't know, let's see, here
some wrong sign right here, and we can just select as all method, use comment key to open
line chart and just ask fix, look at it, the currency conversion logic, you can see there
is another calculation, if fix logic, yeah, okay, we need to specify some more accurate
prompt, of course, you can see it can fix the logic which we broke, yeah, especially the
test case, okay, I hope this quick introduction was useful for you and see you in the next
lesson.